bbnplace.com 2019-05-15

# Privacy Policy

  1. Home
  2. Company
  3. Privacy Policy

#### May 24, 2016

This privacy statement describes how Browser Based Network collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: www.bbnplace.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

#### Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address are collected by payment providers

We use this information to

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Respond to your questions and concerns

#### **Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at info@bbnplace.com

#### **Information Sharing**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order, chat or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.  
We may also disclose your personal information

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if  Browser Based Network is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

#### **Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.  
Our tracking utility company use cookies to retrieve site usage information. The use of cookies by our tracking utility company is not covered by our privacy policy.  We do not have control over these cookies.

#### **Links to Other Web Sites** ** **

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Browser Based Networks. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

#### **Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at admin@bbnplace.com  
When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

Important: Please note that orders made with your Interswitch card or naira mastercard are received and processed directly by Interswitch (via WebPay plugin). We only provide services upon confirmation from the card payment processing company.

#### **Widgets  **

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

#### **Blogs**

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.  
To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at admin@bbnplace.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

#### **Updating/Correcting Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update or delete it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at, support@bbnplace.com

#### **Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account    or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at admin@bbnplace.com.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### **Notification of Privacy Policy Changes**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any change in how we use your personal information we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

#### **Contact Information**

You can contact us by writing or email us at the address below:

**Browser Based Network Ltd.**  
5, Adisa Keshinro Street (Off Abraham Adesanya),  
Ajah – Lekki Phase 2,  
Lagos, Nigeria – 23401  
**Phone:** +234 805 020 9037  
**Email:** info@bbnplace.com
